ADEBAYO VICTOR OLANREWAJU

A competent and committed Business Administration (Actuarial Science) graduate with hands on knowledge and experience of business management processes as well as the planning and practical implementation phases of financial projects. Possessing excellent communication skills and having the ability to communicate professionally with clients and colleagues on detailed financial and managerial issues.

NSQ 2B, F. C. E. (T.), Bichi, P.M.B. 3473, Kano State
Kano
adebayovolanrewaju@yahoo.com
08065095425/08155689115

Experience

Finance and administrative officer Kano Durbar Hotel LTD

2016 - To date

Supervise and direct the financial and accounting activities of the hotel

Safeguard hotel assets, and prepare financial reports in accordance with Generally Accepted Accounting Principles and the Uniform System of Accounts.

Participate in the formation and execution of annual and multi year Business Plans

Pro-actively monitor progress in reaching financial targets for revenue and expense centers and budgeted capital expenditures.

BUDGETING AND FORECASTING ANALYST (INTERN)

First Track Interlinks LTD, Zaria Road Kano

2015 - 2016

Duties:

Participated in calculating future weekly, monthly and yearly budget of the company.

Ensured the breakdown of expenses i.e. monitoring how funds are allocated to help ensure an accurate budget.

Compared the current budget expenditures to the forecasted budget and also determined if the forecasted budget was adhered to; and implemented changes to bring the actual budget more in line with the forecasted budget.

Presented the company's yearly budget to upper management (Chief Financial Officer) for adequate review and approval.

SALES EXECUTIVE / PROCUREMENT OFFICER

First Track Interlinks LTD, Zaria Road Kano

2014 - 2015

Duties:

Procured stocks and delivered top line objective (Volume growth, Market Share) by driving sales, marketing and distributor channel development, FMCG goods (Gongoni Co. insecticides, toiletries and chemicals) Provided monthly sales and market intelligence report to the management.

Education

Master of Business Admin. M.B.A *Bayero University Kano* 2015 - 2016 (Finance and Investment specialization)

Diploma of Chartered Insurance Dip-CIIN Chartered Insurance Institute 2014 - 2015

Professional Diploma in Education (PDE)
Federal College of Education (Technical) Bichi, Kano State.
2014 - 2015

Certificate of Chartered Insurance (CII)
Chartered Insurance Institute of Nigeria
2013 - 2014

BSc. Business Administration (Actuarial Science) 2nd class upper *Ibrahim Badamasi Babangida University Lapai Niger State*. 2008 - 2012

Skills/languages

Microsoft Office software suites (Word, PowerPoint, Excel) Peachtree accounting software Interpersonal communication/relationships
Negotiation skills
Hausa, Yoruba, French, and Spanish languages

Membership

Dip CII®-member, Chartered Insurance Institute of Nigeria (CIIN) 4/19615

Hobbies

Travelling, meeting people, building relationships, listening to people, and playing football.

REFERENCES

Dr. S.A. Okegbile Chief Lecturer, Federal College of Education (T) Bichi, Kano State. asokegbile@yahoo.com Mobile: 08065280733

Mr. Auwal A. Mohammed Chief Executive Officer, First Track Interlinks Services LTD No 23 Zaria Road Kano, Kano State Starlo163@gmail.com Mobile: 08098344771